Wood of Saviours.  Hello, ladies and hello,
babies.  It's just an intro, it seems like
you already get what we're talking about.  For
today's video, we are here in
Landers as you can see and I am in bed
.  Yes, sir.  Why am I so tired?
Because we're going to spend the night at the
grocery store and there's nothing else here.
Okay.  So we're just waiting for those who will
join us.  Of course,
Reynab and Conongy will be with us.  Yes.
First time on my channel.  I'm super
excited.  That's why the content should be explosive
.  What could
these two couples do inside a grocery store without
anyone, without staff, without
anything to do, maybe grocery shopping, eating,
sleeping, whatever?  So I won't
prolong this any longer.  I can only say one thing
to the couple
and of course we will be together for today,
Cong,
of course, my husband, I haven't been
with him in the intro before, that's why Rab
and Conong. What's up,
sister?  What is
your wedding?
Perfect combination, right?
I haven't told you yet, put it in, you're already
insulted, you see, it's
closed,
how did you pay for that,
that's why I said you don't want to go to
our house, not for us to experience, you see,
we're already in a coma.  So if you
sleep inside, you already know.
Combi Rey, I can only say that
I'm thrilled that
my brother is now here on my channel.
We're excited because it's our first time and
we've been hanging out for a while.
That's right.  It seems like
my brother always does something like that when
we hang out.  I'm so scared.
Yes.  Hey, because
Zainab and I had an experience where when we went out,
Zab saw that we were going home.
My brother is already there, as if he's picking me up.  Then
I feel like my brother might think
I'm a bi, they said it's not too much, it's just a few
days away.  In 2018,
I said I needed to get
married so my brother would agree to be
on my channel.
Absolutely no one, yes sir.  What are
we going to do here?  Maybe this can go home
.
If we want to go grocery shopping, go on a
trip, find a place to sleep,
we can do it.  That's why they have the lights on
here.  Oh, nothing.  This can't be turned off, there's a
plan.  There is a plan.
This is fantasy on the
other
hand.  Here I am again.
I'm getting infected with laughter again.  Hey,
I hear about your wise fantasies.  You remember when
you said you were beautiful.
Dear, tell them now
I have talent.  I'm good at
concerts.  Tell me, have
our wives been enlightened?
You know
what our wives' mouths are like, men are like that.
Yes.  You think we don't get caught
every night.
Yes, indeed.  You'll be confused.  Hey, wait a minute.
What do you want to
eat?  Let's talk.  Where have we
landed?
What do you want to eat?  Or first thing is
to find food.  Is it fun?  The
fun.
Your strength is free,
Free.  Free.  Free.  Yes.  Whatever
you take, it's not free.  I will pay
.  But it's free for you.  Anything.   I
love that car.
Why is l a grocery store?
Actually, we don't need the
cart.  Here we go.
Hey, he can afford to buy that.
You are better.  Oh no.  What are you?  You know, I
just started feeling like I had high blood pressure
.  The stone hurts.
We haven't even been together for 20 minutes.
No, I think I saw something right away here
.
Yes.  I saw it right away.   This is a
grocery store.  I will pay.   This is
my thanks to the lander.   It's too much
if we get a lot of it, it's the
first time I've ever entered something like
this, right?
Good morning.  We
only watch this in my movie, the beauty of colas is
fruit, you want it, it's not allowed, let's not
pretend, it's healthy when the
couple is married, I'm not the only one, maybe I
want to change my life, you can call me an
athlete because hey, I
remember, I'm past my bedtime,
what's this, this fills us up,
why can't bananas be sold per piece, it's
okay, we'll take it home, we'll just
take it because that's the
tag.  Let's just not eat this.
Of course there must be bananas.
Yes, it's acidic
because there's no CR here.  Is there a CR here?  That's what
I'm curious about.  Maybe there's some
fun there.  Hello.  Really.  Tell me
why you said we're getting married.  It's not
me anymore.
Hey, why is he running around?  Hey,
I left you alone.  He really took care of
my son.  Is that Kidlat's favorite?
He likes the red one.  The red one is sweet.
My love, please speak.  It's not his
body clock, guys.  I just forced
him.  So, is Bell the quiet one in the morning? It's
really 3:00 a.m.
My body clock says I'm sleeping now.  What do
you want?
What?
Oh, go ahead and take it.
Go.
Zinab will cook what we're going to eat
tonight.
Yes.
What do you want?  Just cream cheese is enough
.
Yes.  What?  What do you want?  That's
cream cheese, right?
What kind of cream cheese is that?  I don't
know that.
There you go.  This.  This.
Okay.  How many?
M is just
one
love.  You know their cart is full.
We only have one like this.  Did
we really say that?
Yes.  What can we eat?
Wheat bread.
Wheat bread.  There he is in
his health.
Wheat bread.
No.  What we should do is find something
we can cook because they have appliances
.
There you go.  Make me some calamari
here.
Maybe even if they let us go, they'll let us go
.
Hey, we don't have any water yet.
There's coconut.
Hey, can we drink that here?
Zeab,
can we drink this now?
Yes, there is no cashier.  Where do we
pay?  We'll put everything in
one car and then have it all punched out
.  So can I drink here?
Yes, you can come,
we'll ask the librarian first.
Hey, it's delicious to drink coconut water at a
grocery store that's closed.   They say that
happiness is like a fantasy for
young people, she's like, oh my god,
I'm really happy right now.  We have a lot to
do.  Hey, I see it now
.   It's
not just delicious because we're here at a
closed grocery store.
He is a fantasy.  It's
free.
You know, we're really good troops.
I have acid reflux.  You're so good at inviting
wine too.  I also make wine.  Oh yes,
I have severe acid reflux because I eat one meal a day
.  So he triggers before the
first meal.  It's like
my chon is begging for it.  Eat now.  Eat now.  I was
forbidden from
eating too much.  It's good to
eat more, but only little by little.
Mm.  No bombing.  No
bombs.  No bombs.  I'm going to bomb.   I will
bomb you.  Hey, okay.   My
love, you know we need to learn from
your silence.   Is
n't he like that to you?
He's like that when there's no one around.
Pillow.  There's a pillow.
Hey, your decision is right.  Take one.  Hey, that's
two.  One by one.
Oh, how nice it is to sleep.
Why did you take it?  Where is it?
That's two.  You are alone.  I love you.
Why don't you choose a nice, quality
pillow and let's sleep there.  Isn't
there a phone here?   Do
you want it tough?  I also want it to be
hard.
You know, those wives are so pig-
mouthed.
Those are the things he takes from you
.  Zab's mouth is strong.  What?
You're the only person who can talk like that
.  That's right.  What is that, sister?  Sis,
why?  Where are you?  Here.
That's it, behave.  Let's find a king
size to fit our bed.  How is
this?  Queen.  Queen full.
You know we need to take this down.
Hey, we still don't have enough food.  You're so mean that
you'll only feed me bananas and that's it
.  Oh,
you better stay away from there.  Oh
basketball.  Hey, why
play basketball?  You even challenged Rey
here because the
pair didn't know who to focus on.
Hey, we don't have any sensible food and
water
later, what's the deal with that?
The water was easy to find
and Cong's cart was beautiful.
Look.  Where can I
put it,
I want the two king
sizes, did you take them?  It should be something
you can take home.  This should be
your king-size bed.  What is our bed?
I don't know.  Oh oh oh oh oh.  Do
you want a different color?
Oh.  This.  This.
How many?  Two.
Just one.  Just one.  Just one of these.
That's okay.  This is a win.
Okay.  Next.  Cookies bread.  Maybe
lightning is needed.  I don't have a
gift for him yet.  I wasn't able to attend
their birthday.  You're already one of us, so it's going to be hard to
carry.
The size of the kya
sis.  I appreciate you.  But how can
we, as a couple, bottle this?  It's not
boxed.  Is this
it?
Yes, that's right.  Basketball, basketball,
dear B. I saw water on
stage, I just found it.  What kind of water is
that?  'Why are you trying this ionized
alkaline water essential plus, I'm just
seeing what else is healthy about
alkaline water?  Alkaline.
That's great for acidic dry waters.   Is that
right?  He's not honest,
he has something better.  Yes, it varies.  Alkaline is alkaline, but
I just see it as a different size.
We are still in distinct, Zinop is already
in alkaline.  We're not at
that level yet.  Let's also do some
camping camping movies for this, here's the
content you want to watch
so we can see if they'll be able
to produce
children first.  Oh, not a tent, a tent, a
tent again.  Don't do it too soon.
That's what I heard my wife say too
.  Every word that comes out here makes
me proud.  Haven't you
gotten infected from your husband's mouth yet?
I just kept quiet.  Or why?
This also always bothers me
.  So guys, my bangs are not in
order because of too much excitement.  Hey,
Cong and I just bonded like
this.  Thank you so much, sister, for being
here.  I'll buy you a poem.  I don't want
you to trip me up.  I didn't need to
trip you up?
I don't cheat on my wife.
That's all.  E. Hey hey hey
don't be hey what
you're eating hurry up I'll be there baby bye
you let him have the strength of the right one come on
the strength of the right one
I'll get him
or sig Reay to the rescue.  Bro,
take care of yourself, bro.  Shoot him, okay,
bro.  That's conditioning so that when you return
to the league, we can get 10,000 steps.
That's it, love, Reay will shoot you
here.
Bow.  This is even easier.  There you go.  These are the
two.  There's the bow.
Let's go.  Alan or that.  Or jump.
This is the one that is raging.   It's
crazy.  We are like children here.  Oh, how
fun.  We can play
this.  I just see it from somewhere.  We can't
go camping.  Yes.
Smart people are not good either.  Yes, indeed
.  Oh, let's play a game.  Let's see
who will win.  Please allow
us to go on our trip first.  We will give it to you
.
Okay.  Rock rock pic.  Who will go first?  Stone
stone pick.  Yes, we are the black team
or
you, let
's let them be happy first,
break it,
sorry,
let's keep fighting back
as if we were already winning, square by
square,
we'll lose,
I didn't think I got a grade two,
I just thought your brain was asleep, this is a bit
intense, huh.
No one speaks because no one wants
to lose.
Come back with the
correct outfit.
Back.
There you go.  1 2 3 4 Okay, okay, okay, sleepy, getting
married,
Hey, he's happy, he's happy, in
fairness, the competitiveness came out,
wow, help me here, B test, let's go there
.  No, no.  No no no
no two are big.  Of course,
we know how to handle things like that, sis.
That's right, we're on their trip.
Okay, kids, you might get lost in that.   What can
I do?  Grill.
Grilled.
I said why
Kobe Kobe
Kobe.
Hey, where will it hit?  Oh,
even if you just hit it
.  That's what the stone is like.  It looks like this.
Yes.  It seems like that, I really don't know.
You did that, so what
?  It's not like if you hit him,
that's three points.
So one point one point
you threw him away then there was a little
twist so he could have lunch.
So two point
2 one yes first to 10 okay
hey still got stronger cameraman even though you hit him
.  What should be here?  He went up to
Yes, just go up, just go up.
Just come up.
Oh, look at
GGI too.  What is that and sports?
If you shoot, you get more points.  Three
points.
Three.  That's three points.
Hey,
oh.
Ah, short
class.
How is it done?  Look,
I hit that.  Hit me
so I can push it.  How can I hit
that?  I can't even put it in the box.
Hey,
hit.
Are you angry?  I can't shoot.  Oh,
finally.
It's me.
Game ball.   He even
shot the last one he didn't give us when
we were playing
.  Prove who you are to make
jokes.
Or you didn't win earlier.  At least
we are all one now.  All one all one.  All one
or I did
n't do what I did earlier.  Why
was it taught?  It's just late.  They don't
teach, they teach solidly the first time
.  Brother, when you have another match on
ABS-CBN, you will make this your trainer.  Yes,
you know that, man.  Oh, shot.  There's
Alfonso there.  There is Alfonso.
No more.  No one drinks here anymore.
Are Sister B and I retired?  Yes, no more.   There are
no more drinks like that
.  Okay.  The next thing we need to do is
be a chair there because we're going to set up
our food?  Let's go on a
food trip.  We haven't had a food trip.
Yes, indeed.  We only have bananas.  What
we need, sister, is bread.
Yes,
there is.   I think this will
make healthy food.
Turkeys are arrogant.  We have nothing to
contribute.  What can we give?
I told you to make calamari.
You don't have any meat there.  They warned us that
we would burn.  These are
camping chairs.  Choose a color.  There's
black, there's burgundy, there's green.  What
color do you want it to be?  That's it.  It is
black.  Yes.  There you go.  So
we can sit down somewhere because what we're doing is tiring.
We can take 10,000 steps here.
too big.
You know we haven't gotten to that
part yet.   Are
you tired?  Be quiet.
Yes, indeed.  I'm tired.
The boys are just recharging.  Go get some food.
We're going to set up the lights in the
house.  Light?
Light of the house.   Do
you think there is a hole?
Mouth.
Actually,
these are the mouths of the home.
I'll fix it.  Just buy food.  Tied up.
You know you can have a movie rom.
You don't want to produce a movie.  I love
watching movies, sis.  You can do that
no matter what kind of trip you're going on
.  You can do it.  Everything about how cute
my wife is, how I got
married,
your channel is full of her.  Yes,
no.  Mm.  It's like he's a branch of his channel,
my channel is a
branch.  What should we do?  Let's fix what
we have.  We're here so
the seat is there.
You know I can really sleep at 4:00.
At least
you didn't see me sleeping, really sleeping.  In
fairness, no, we haven't
been camping yet, we're camping in the
lander.
Okay, that's fine.
What is sleeping?
I am sleeping.  4:00 5:00.  But earlier
I slept because I felt like I needed it,
I said I need strength for what it is,
4 in the morning,
yes I went to sleep, I wake up around 10 or
11 in the morning,
so you sleep 5 or 6 hours,
yes 10 or 11 is hard,
12 is
hard, because you are an athlete, you
need 8 hours of sleep,
really 8 hours of sleep,
really 8 hours to be really full, if
your head hurts too much, you can do
that, 5 is enough, but he really doesn't
want it.
Beer, brother, I'm already negative about beer.
I found potato chips.  On the other hand, I think
they'll take this.  Banana chips.
That's too healthy for them.  Ah,
they need to eat those
things.
Mm.
This is delicious, worth trying.
What is this?   Is
he
really Chips?
Mm.  That's a win, hunters.
Bia loves that kind of thing.  The
really spicy ones?  He's getting spicy.
Mm.
How old is he?  Five?
Six five when you fry tilapia,
she's tired of it, Bi is really spicy,
Lucas is not, oh, just right,
Viia is more spicy.
He is really looking for it.
Yes.
Mm.  But how is Kitkat?  He doesn't like
spicy food because when he was a child,
we were on a plane once.  B tried
some food without B being aware that
the food was spicy.
He was so surprised that he looked like he was 2 years old
.  He cried on the plane because
he seemed to be traumatized so when
we said it was spicy he didn't get
upset anymore now when he has
something he wants to eat
we say spicy he didn't get
upset anymore
wow
oh sweet
you know we bought this potato here
we've been going around for a while oh potato
what is that bread what does it taste like
you know I want real food
I'm hungry it's
not tasty you seem stingy you
seem like
you won't like this why why oh why oh
your traffic I'll get your chips.  Just wait,
I'll get your chips here.  It seems like it.  Okay guys,
I'm okay here.  You're seventy,
right?  Just a claimant.
We save everything we take, even the
trash.  Because
we will pay for this.  So you might think
we're wasting our time on groceries.  Well, if
possible, we don't mess up and
we put the things we move back to their rightful place
.  So thank you so much for
sharing our trip.  It's clear.
Nothing.  Just warm up for now.  He used to
come home around 9:00 in the morning.  Because this is just a 5:00
warm-up.  There's no alcohol when there's
alcohol.  Because if you have alcohol, you won't
really get sleepy.
Really?  That makes me sleepier
.  What has changed between you two
now that you both have children?  You can't
make decisions on
your own, those spontaneous plans
.  Because, for example, especially in
our work, they will be harmed if they are implicated
.  Yes.  So our nonsense is funny,
but that's what makes it
different now.  Now
we think more before we do anything.
Because we used to be girls,
so when they grow up, they can
see that.  When they saw that, they said, "
Oh, my mother used to be like that."  So
he's not a good example.
That's why I'm going to delete
my other videos.   Did
you know that we watched
our first video in the asylum
7 years ago?
That's terrible.  7 years ago.
You're still chubby, aren't you?
Yes, yes.  It's like we smell sour, but
our faces are different
.  Now the glow up is serious.  Is that how a
ring is put on
someone's heart when they love him/her?
Exactly.
You guys are getting married now,
what has changed for you guys and what are
you happiest about it?
For me, that sense of family is really what
I was looking for.  I'm just a kid so
I'm ready.  Saaba family when
you three came into my life.  So maybe that
's the biggest thing for me.
Patience just grows.  Really patient.
Patience is awesome when it's really,
really patience.  Actually that's what we always
lose.  He's running out of patience with
me because we both have different energy levels
.  Okay.  Yes, because he is an unknown aspect
of our lives.  What is it like to have a
child of a child?  So it's like
he's a test of your new personality because
he's completely different from what
you're used to because
you're going to be a father, this is where you'll learn
patience.  You can learn a lot,
especially while traveling with
your kids.  Because that's where you'll feel
all the hardships of traveling with
children.  And the fun, of course, is
the most delicious of all the
memories.
Those memories are what you are
as a person, what you will grow into.  Because
you will learn how to do what you need to do,
what kind of patience
you need to have.  "You don't
expect that you have that kind of
patience. Before, small
things used to irritate you, but now that you have a child, that's
no longer possible.
Your patience must be on a different level."
So those are the ones that seem to have improved
us, as for me personally, as for
me, I also agree on
that point, the three of us.  Yes, it's not different,
why are you with us? But you're
with me, you're also with my brother's patience,
so he'll give you patience, because
the two are still young. I
feel like he's more patient with
me than with the kids, because with the
kids, when he loses his patience,
he can scold me, tell me off. It's really
not his patience. I can see that
his hand is shaking sometimes,
because sometimes, so that he doesn't have any more
patience. Ah,
I thought, I thought, because one day,
I told you
what happened
when you were working.
Yes,
I'm so tired.  He wants
to play, daddy, can you put down your
cellphone please?  Ah yes,
children are like that because when you're on the phone,
sometimes they demand attention, but
especially in our line of work, we're
also on the phone.  So what did he tell
you? I checked my emails, right? Is
n't that the contracts?
He said, "Daddy, can you put down
your phone?"  I want to play.
I hung up the phone immediately.
I felt like I could feel
his genuineness, when he was acting like that.  I said,
"Yes, work will be later."
And honestly, we won't have a
hard time making decisions like that
if you know your priorities.  Mm.
Because you know our children are your priority
.  You know Viia is your priority
.  So when he asked if
you could put your phone down,
you were able to decide quickly
because you knew your priorities.
He's just a good reminder.  I think
I appreciate him for being like that.
Ask questions.
Yes, ask.  Daddy, can you put on your
phone please?  I want to play.  You're right,
son.  You're right.  Thank you for
spending my time.  Spend time.  Well, it's leaving now
.  Yes, indeed.  He's only a few days old.  Three.
Yes.  And then there's what you said earlier,
I had an experience with Kidlat.
Anyway, I'm doing live selling.
After I sold live, she cried.
He said, "I'm going to put him to sleep,
"Mommy, put me to sleep first." Oh,
I put him to sleep. My plan was to
just put him to sleep and then I'll come down.
He asked me. He was already lying down. He said,
"Mommy, why are you working?"
I said, "So we can buy some
toys.  We can go to Japan,
you can have a birthday, you can go on an airplane."
He sat down. He said, "Mommy, haven't
we been to Japan?  I have so many
Spider-Man.  "I've had a birthday."
That's right.
Do you know what I did?
Seriously,
you ended the live?
I didn't go live
.
I put him to sleep. It's great.
They remind us of the real
situation
of what is
really important. That's true
because sometimes we are so busy with the speed
of life with so much to do, with the
content we think about like this and that,
right? It's
draining sometimes. It's like when
they're there, it's like we're being recharged.
Yes. Then you'll see them there,
they'll remind you that these are the
important little moments
that are happening in our lives right now,
especially with the kids.
Besides, how can you
avoid it because there's also mom and dad guilt that's
called that. So it seems like
you can avoid it. I think all
parents have experienced that, especially when
we work. We
feel like that every time
we can't give them what they want.
So it's like when they say something, it's
automatic, right away, right away.
Especially with toys, for example
although I try to control it but
you know it seems like you feel like that's the
way to get back at them. But in
short, it's
so fulfilling, it feels
so happy. You make your child happy,
the smile, the
quality time they enjoy. It's
different. Earlier today,
Kidlat shot for the first time in the basketball ring. It was
his first time throwing it like that.
The ball reached the high ring. He
shot and shot. He shot and shot. So those are the
moments.
That's when he looked at
my reaction and his daddy's reaction that
he shot. He looked first and then
he celebrated. When that's what's
important to him. Core memory,
I guess. Their core memory. And then it's not
obvious that we love
our children very much. In the many places
in the grocery store,
we are in the kids area.
You're in Lego. What's in And
then I saw what I was taking home for
them.
Exactly? That's what I said  It's different
because when we leave them
and they don't know we left but
for us it's our guilt. So
when we go home, what do
we have for them? It's always like that.
No matter where you go, we went on our whole Europe
trip, each of our staff
just bought gifts for
everyone in Paris, but all
our stuff like in each city,
we only bought Lucas and Bia, just so
they would think we bought them like this,
they're the only ones who have a
good childhood, we're still doing it, madam, how many are
soon, how many are the plans,
I want three plus 3 more plus 3 more but it's one
after another, it should be one after another, it's
too much to be
one, just go back and glow up. Yes
. It's hard when you skip,
yes. If we get pregnant, a boy,
then you lose weight again, then
you get pregnant again. You're the
next one. I'm praying that we'll have twins
soon. Do you have twins?
My mother has a cousin.  he is a twin
then he also has a second cousin.
They have a chance. I hope they are really twins.
That's perfect. Boy and girl. No more. we are
so are you related do you have any of us have
asthma eh
asthma not kambalang have asthma
b has as asthma does kidlat have yes
I remember his story now one
time that it was necessary what is that e siblings
eh allergic rhinitis there is the
asthma asthma wedding wedding bright mates
sister b and I already have a dress
she just came to our ceremony to
leave right away because you were expecting
kidlat but we appreciated that
I was surprised because we didn't meet when
I saw the video they were there they
really came because of course sis
we really wanted to see
we appreciate that of course you know priority
really kids when they are the ones in the way you
don't have to cancel everything exactly everything everything
good your grocery store wasn't canceled
one of my bucket list in my
YouTube career because you can collaborate with brother
I said earlier what did I say?
I'm afraid to intro in front of him. Yeah.  I'm
ashamed. I'm ashamed of you. I don't
really feel like I always say this in
interviews. I mean, if I hadn't
become friends with your squad,
I feel like I wouldn't have done YouTube. My
sister always says, "You should log in,
you're so noisy."  That's how you look, that's how
noisy you are.  "That's your vlog." Then
of course you're the ones I was with,
awesome. So until now
my lookup is still there. Fan girl
suddenly fell in love. Look at it even if
you combine our subscribers.
You're awesome. It doesn't mean, it doesn't
mean look at what you've reached
now, you really deserve it and
you're really for that. But I always look back
always and forever, my respect for
you. These things are really awesome too
and that's why I'm super happy that I'm finally here. Yes,
this content is beautiful. Do
you know this is our fantasy? We haven't
experienced it yet. I thought
I was a fantasy artist because it's my fantasy.
That's true. What else is this fantasy?
Maybe you have something else, what else is this
fantasy of yours? We have a child named
Landers,
why is it called Toky? When lightning struck,
the buga hit, yes, it was raining, because it was like
lightning when he arrived,
no, the one who freed you was the one who gave you
that nickname, it's really Junyie,
okay, so there's no connection, he was made in
Tokyo, I hope so, but in the
but in the park, the ugly
park is here.  we are from
Paranaque from Parque Paranque we were
born there but it's ugly because oh
park come on let's go more
atina more atina more
atina but you know you look like Tokyo
as in as in kid this looks like
kidlat halo halo that's also not but
you can really see it when kidlat is
kong and toky is kid
even his attitude even kidlat's attitude everything
about him?
Yes.
Tokyo is easy for me. It's easy. It
seems shy.
How did you do that? How?
That's a combination. It's a
combination.
Helicopter. Helicopter
. It's beautiful how you did
it. Helicopter. Helicopter. This is the
mother of the collab. That's because we're done
chatting. We've been chatting for a long time
. There are so many cuts there. Apart from that
you saw we had a chat
without a camera. Yes. And it's early in the morning
because it's morning, the cashier is about to open
. Our two carts
earlier were already at the cashier. Let
's add what are the
We need it. Because let's make the most of it.
We can only do groceries once
without anyone.
Yes. Let's go.
Let's go.
Enjoy it.
Yes. It's our first time experiencing it.
Hey, you're here. I didn't expect
to meet at the grocery store. You're the same
. Have you been here a while?
Just arrived.
You thought we were already drunk. You thought we hadn't
talked for five hours. We're the
best of the landers. Think about it.
Good. We're the first customers. We're the
first to get punch there because they
open their boxes at 8:00 a.m. But
they actually open at 9: a.m. The smell is
there. Pure ano,
pure soap.
It's fun.
Spicy. Chili garlic. I haven't tried
that yet.
Chili garlic. How many?
Yehey! I've been
grocery shopping and I'm already tired.
I've already walked 10,000 steps. Hi brother.
There are some ano workers here now. It's
so nice to go grocery shopping
You're just pushing. Hey, dear, refined or. MG is melting, no,
where are you talking about, what are you saying, what is
thermal, yes, dear, let's add it, but what is
assorted, okay
That's all
we need at home. Is
the hilod gone? Okay, that's it. Why do
you look dizzy?
And we're done.
Morning. Oh, our roll opened.
So sister B and brother Cong went first
because you know the young ones have school,
of course
we need to settle what's bothering
us here in Lander. So many many
many many thanks to Ate V and
brother Kong and of course
Mr. and Mrs. Velasquez and Mr. and
Mrs. Sparks were able to do the grocery shopping. Yes. That's the
good ending of the vlog and I hope
you're happy with this collab. And also watch out for
our collab on Ate B's channel
and subscribe to brother Kong too. Thank
you so much for watching this video and
thank you to my husband.
Thank you. Thank you for the experience,
my dear, you know why thank you, you
paid for this kind of content,
my card is the one that gets scratched. Now
your card is different, it's ours. It's ours
. Many many many thanks to you and
brother Cong for that, in a heartbeat, it's
an honor.
Yes. So that's where we're ending
this vlog. Sebbies, hope you like this
video. Please don't forget to like,
share, subscribe, and click notification
bell for more updates and for more
upcoming
videos.
I love you allies. Bye. Do share, do
share, do share. Mwah. Hala, maybe
they'll see you last in the vlog. Tagan lang
talaga. Back to work. Let's just go to
Japan. Bye.
I see you moving up. Hey, me
your day.
I'm your I was your girlfri Eh